Clear.
Left flank clear.
Cover!
Rockets!
Is everyone alright?
Spread out!
Deploy smoke grenades!
Squad Leader, hurry and send it!
We're running out of time!
The Blue Force command post isn't confirmed yet.
Send what?
Let's take out the Blue Force's combat forces first.
We can send it to the command post later.
I'll draft the message right now.
That's not right.
Their mission isn't a Decapitation Strike.
Then their mission is...
To provide an Incision Point for the Decapitation Strike.
This is the future direction of special ops units.
How could I have overlooked this?
Then just now,
we've already exposed many targets.
We can't let them send out the coordinates.
Staff Officer Zhu!
Yes, sir!
Initiate Full-spectrum Electronic Jamming immediately!
Turn the power to maximum!
Switch all internal comms to wired connections.
Yes, sir!
Activate the jamming system immediately!
Squad Leader, I can't hold on!
Almost done!
Report!
The island-wide jamming systems are activating.
Did it work?
We lost the signal.
Even if the jamming and transmission were simultaneous,
as long as Lin Yihu pressed the send button,
we can ensure the message was sent successfully.
We've tested it many times before.
Report!
Speak.
Message received from Morning Cloud Island.
A total of 12 targets.
Sender: Lin Yihu.
Execute the strike immediately.
Yes, sir.
Way to go, Lin Yihu.
That's great.
Lin Yihu,
you've finally turned the tables this round.
Squad Leader!
Squad Leader, we succeeded! Squad Leader!
Squad Leader, look, we succeeded.
We succeeded, Squad Leader.
Squad Leader Wu, I succeeded.
I didn't...
I didn't let him down.
Huzi!
I saw it.
You succeeded.
You did it.
Squad Leader Wu.
Did you see that?
We succeeded.
I didn't let you down.
Understood.
Everyone, pull back to the command post.
Everyone, fall back now.
Don't get so worked up.
Guo Zijian has the New-type Combat System.
On this point,
we can't compare to him.
He can Command the wind and rain now.
With the battle at this point,
firepower and missiles are useless.
Staff Officer Zhu!
Yes, sir!
Order the surveillance squad
to closely monitor all cameras in the command post.
I want to see
how Guo Zijian
infiltrates my heart and brain.
Yes, sir!
Let's see what this kid is really capable of.
Report!
Speak.
We still can't contact anyone on the frontline.
It seems they've set up on the island
high-power information jamming equipment.
That means we've been forcibly stripped
of contact with the frontline special ops.
Alright.
Since we can't make contact,
we might as well
all stay in the dark together.
What do you mean?
It's their home turf now.
Guo Zijian is short on manpower,
he can't make contact,
and is on the defensive at every turn.
So we might as well
destroy all the power equipment
on the entire island,
so Long Yuanshan won't have an advantage either.
You want to use a Graphite bomb?
Order:
Immediately access the top-tier combat system
and request the use of a Graphite bomb.
Yes, sir!
Beihua,
did you see that?
The Wind Rider Battalion is requesting a Graphite bomb.
In our exercises,
we've rarely used tactics like this.
It's just too powerful.
Young guys these days will try anything.
I'll support it as long as it helps us win.
My only regret is
that the power grid on this island
is too small.
What a waste of my perfectly good Graphite bomb.
Old Zhang, did you see that?
Beihua has even learned to be thrifty now.
Activate backup power immediately.
Yes, sir. Activating now.
Report! Backup power has been destroyed.
It cannot be activated.
The circuits are destroyed. It's a Graphite bomb.
Comrades.
It is obvious
that the Red Army used a Graphite bomb.
But even so,
there are only a few dozen Red Army soldiers on the island.
And after our multiple strikes,
there are barely any left.
Our special ops team is more than enough to handle them.
Now, I order
all personnel to prepare for combat.
Yes, sir.
To be reborn from desperation.
That was a ruthless move by Guo Zijian.
How many men are left in the special ops team?
They've been in constant crossfire.
Let me get a count.
Notify the troops immediately.
Hold your positions and stand by.
Do not engage proactively.
Judging by the effect of their mobile warfare,
their personnel are highly capable.
The fewer their numbers,
the easier it is for them to operate.
We can't let them gain an advantage.
Yes, sir.
Jiang Shengqiang did a beautiful job.
Honey Badger, Siberian Tiger.
Report your current personnel status.
Report!
Honey Badger team currently has five combatants.
Siberian Tiger team currently has four combatants.
Copy that.
I assess
that the Blue Army command post
is located in Building 13, southwest corner.
Choose your approach routes carefully,
and advance stealthily.
Understood.
Honey Badger copies.
Move out.
Do you three know
why you are the key protection targets
of our squad?
The drones.
Exactly.
Your mission now
is to return to the drone hideout.
When the time is right,
launch the drone swarm
to execute the final strike on the Blue Army.
Understood.
Zhao Xiaoyun, Ma Zhengzheng.
Here!
Your core mission
is to keep Dongfang safe.
Understood?
Understood.
Move out.
Reporting, Sirs.
Due to their ultimate move with the Graphite bomb,
which we truly didn't anticipate,
Exercise Control cannot provide real-time video.
We've coordinated with the Navy for support.
They will dispatch a small communication ship,
equipped with a base station,
to ensure uninterrupted wireless communication.
It's been confirmed.
The Red Army currently has only three teams.
Each team has four or five men.
Don't underestimate these three teams.
Especially that Yang Maolin.
I know.
I've fought him before.
He's got some skills.
But it doesn't matter.
In modern warfare,
a single bullet will still kill him.
Actually, with just those few men of his,
even if we lined up at the command post,
he still couldn't break in.
What's the situation now?
Right now, except for our second floor,
every other floor
has men stationed.
Good.
Then let's wait for him to walk right into the trap.
Report. Everything is ready on our end.
It's not time yet.
Do not launch a strike prematurely.
Still not attacking?
Wait any longer and you'll all be KIA.
It'll be too late.
Await my command.
Your current mission
is to monitor the second floor from all angles
and wait for my hand signals.
I don't see you on the second floor.
You will in a moment.
Copy that.
Honey Badger.
Honey Badger, copy.
I'll go turn myself in first.
I'll be right behind to protect you.
Brigadier Long.
Look who's here.
Guo Zijian.
Shouldn't you be at the command post?
What brings you here?
Leading men onto the island yourself.
Don't tell me you're plotting another trick.
You've already captured me.
What tricks could I possibly have?
One Graphite bomb,
and you really think you've won?
Your naivety is quite adorable, Little Guo.
You know that, right?
If my calculations are correct,
you only have Yang Maolin left,
holding out with three rookies.
But...
our battalion command post is still active.
My detachment is still here.
True.
But even if your Amphibious Infantry Fighting Vehicle lands,
it won't solve your pressing need.
Not to mention, my Ultra-long-range Strike Force
has already targeted the perimeter of Morning Cloud Island.
None of your forces have a chance to enter anymore.
So,
Brigadier Long has definitely won this round.
Do you still think you can turn the tables?
Guo Zijian.
You don't even have a trump card left.
I actually thought
we'd have a fierce showdown.
Too bad you didn't make it to the end.
You have no combat power left.
In short,
the battle is over.
Now it's our turn.
This scenario
took a turn way too fast.
Different equipment, different tactics,
and even different generations of weapons
can replace and cancel each other out.
But only the human element
in this showdown of brand-new equipment
leaves us with endless food for thought.
I announce
that this exercise
is now concluded.
The 396th Brigade and the Wind Rider Battalion are victorious.
Staff Officer Liang, did you see that?
Today's victory is exactly like you said.
On the battlefield of the future,
gender will no longer be a barrier.
The age of armor is over!
Battalion Commander Guo is so awesome!
Battalion Commander Guo!
Battalion Commander Guo, you're awesome!
Stop shouting.
He has no signal or power over there.
He can't hear you.
Staff Officer Liang.
Are you crying, Staff Officer Liang?
No, I'm not.
Staff Officer Liang, why are you crying?
Hey guys, Staff Officer Liang is crying!
Staff Officer Liang!
For our victory, Staff Officer Liang
has shed tears of joy!
Staff Officer Liang!
I'm not!
Squad Leader Hong, could you
please help me
wipe away Staff Officer Liang's tears of joy?
Keep shouting!
Roger!
Yeah!
Do you know what I'm thinking right now?
I'm not a mind reader, sir.
I remember personally telling you to join the Challenge.
You kid,
actually didn't show your Brigade Commander any respect.
I also remember
when I invited you to the 404th Brigade,
you actually turned me down.
Seeing my value so early on,
you're practically my talent scout.
Still as arrogant as ever.
Brigadier Long,
thank you for your support and encouragement.
Thank you.
Guo Zijian,
your value...
this is only the beginning.
I believe that
as the Value Cube turns,
you, and your Wind Rider Battalion,
will definitely bring the entire army's
combat capability development
much more profound reflection.
Keep up the good work.
I guarantee the mission will be accomplished.
Old Commander,
I brought a couple of soldiers.
This is my Old Commander, Chen Hanxiao.
And this is Staff Officer Liang Hong.
Chairman Chen.
And this
is the Battalion Commander of the Wind Rider Battalion, Guo Zijian.
Dad.
What did you call him?
My father, Comrade Chen Hanxiao.
Are you serious?
Pure bloodline, 100 percent genuine.
He's my biological father.
And Auntie Guo, Guo Yunqing.
I never would've guessed.
You kept me in the dark this whole time.
And... and this girl too.
Old Commander.
Look at your whole family,
keeping us all guessing.
He's in the military, and we didn't want to interfere.
So...
No wonder you, kid,
could reach out across the whole country
and pull in all kinds of military equipment as aid.
Turns out
you had such a strong backing.
I'm flattered, but I can't take the credit.
Old Commander.
Like father, like son.
Guo Zijian.
He's truly excellent and well-rounded.
I should thank you.
Zijian being where he is today
is all thanks to the military's training.
All right.
You young people are all gathered here today.
Go talk about your youthful topics.
Give my Old Commander back to me.
We old buddies need to catch up.
Okay.
Yes, sir.
You just wait, kid.
Totally unexpected. I didn't see it coming.
You're really something.
Battalion Commander.
Old Commander, I often think about
that time you led us in that
battalion-scale combat.
In that battle, in terms of troops and firepower,
we didn't have an overwhelming advantage.
But we still fought.
You were skilled at troop deployment,
you dared to strike,
and you dared to show the Drawing Sword spirit.
Looking at the combat results,
we not only thwarted the enemy's follow-up plans,
but also crushed their arrogance.
As Chinese soldiers,
we have, time and time again,
been forced into passive positions.
But every time, we managed to turn the tide.
Besides historical opportunities and the people's support,
the most important thing is
that we have the correct leadership of the Party,
and the fearless spirit
of us Chinese soldiers.
Speaking of which,
our army
hasn't fought a war in over 30 years.
But I believe
that if anyone dares to provoke us,
Chinese soldiers will not hesitate.
Well said.
Report!
Come in.
Commanders,
since we rarely get together like this,
how about we take a group photo?
Sure. All right.
Old Commander, come here.
You stand in the middle.
Right here.
Liang Beihua.
Sir!
Your troops took the top prize this time.
Say a few words.
I'll go first?
Please.
Sirs, Comrades,
In this exercise,
Comrade Guo Zijian
and his Wind Rider Battalion
through rich battlefield practice
have already given a detailed elaboration.
Regarding this point,
I will not say more.
What I do want to say is,
as the Wind Rider Battalion has come this far,
I feel deeply moved.
I remember a certain saying,
"Theory is always gray,
only the tree of practice is ever green."
The Wind Rider Battalion,
I have accompanied its practice,
seen its hardships,
and witnessed their struggles.
However,
the drive for a strong army by taking the initiative
and proactively seeking change has not changed.
"You fight your way, I fight my way,"
this Essence of Combat
and military thinking has not changed.
At the same time,
the Chinese military's
Blood-Red Military Soul,
its character and spirit have not changed.
Comrades,
in a context where the global military revolution
is in full swing, looking at the Army,
our Wind Rider Battalion
has merely taken the first step in this exploration.
Therefore, I want to appeal here
to agencies at all levels
and leaders at all levels
regarding our Wind Rider Battalion:
offer more criticism,
more support, and more encouragement.
Give them more opportunities to hone themselves,
and offer more wisdom to assist them.
Thank you all.
Comrade Beihua said it well.
I completely agree.
Ever since soldiers existed,
this profession has only one core mission.
That is to win.
If you cannot win,
no matter how complete your army's other functions are,
or how beautiful and perfect,
they will lose their foundation for existence.
Over the past two days,
while watching the exercise,
I have also been thinking
about the Chinese Army
and where it should head.
Its direction of development...
What is the Army's
most correct direction for progress?
Right now, we have the Wind Rider Battalion.
Some might say
that it is.
But you could also say
it is not entirely.
Development
is always dynamic.
We cannot set any undertaking
as a static coordinate.
However,
development
must have a basic reference.
So we can say
the Wind Rider Battalion's exploration
has at least
for the road ahead of us
discovered
valuable experience
for advancing further.
Guo Zijian!
Here!
Beautifully done.
Keep up the good work.
Comrade Guo Zijian
as the representative
of the young soldiers' exploration,
fills my heart with excitement
and boundless passion.
It gives me reason
to be proud of our ambitious
and highly capable subordinates.
I have every reason
to envision our
future Army
serving as
the powerful backbone of the nation,
filling me with hope and confidence.
Old Liu.
How can you just leave like this?
Alright, say no more.
I've already made up my mind.
Zijian.
In the past,
I gave you a hard time.
I hope you don't take it to heart.
You're a real man.
You've earned my respect.
Take care.
But Old Jiang, you can't give up.
You're the model soldier of our brigade.
When have I ever given up?
I'm all sweaty.
What are you doing? Let me give you a hug.
Alright.
Since you're already out here,
walk me to the gate.
You thought I'd only walk you this far?
Let's go.
I saw the transfer order.
It's not the institute from last time.
This time it's the Army Research Institute.
Is it related to this exercise?
Our Wind Rider Battalion
stood out in this exercise.
They want to transfer me over
to continue research on the Combined Arms Battalion.
That's a good thing.
You're moving on to bigger things.
Guo Zijian.
Thank you.
Thank you
for always looking out for me.
You kept your promise to me.
In the Wind Rider Battalion, I truly
experienced
the pride and sense of mission of a soldier.
To me, these are all very,
very precious experiences.
Actually, speaking of thanks,
I should be the one thanking you.
For everything.
Are your bags all packed?
All packed.
Is this all of it?
I didn't have much stuff to begin with.
I've already shipped most of it.
Let's go. I'll see you off.
It's almost time.
Let's just say goodbye here.
Guo Zijian
Although we're on different paths now,
our destination is the same.
I believe it won't be long
before you meet a better version of me.
I look forward to our reunion,
and to better versions of ourselves.
Liang Hong
I'll wait for you.
The global landscape is ever-changing.
Deputy Battalion Commander,
the exercise is about to begin.
Notify all personnel of the Wind Rider Battalion.
Move out!
Yes, sir!
Orders!
First and Second Companies,
flank the north side of Kaizhou Mountain.
Launch the drones.
Target the Jiahe Valley area
and conduct reconnaissance by fire.
Execute!
Yes, sir!
Report.
The comrade from the Army Combat Research Center is here.
Staff Major Liang Hong,
ordered to assist the 396th Brigade in this exercise.
Conflicts persist across the globe.
The flames of war have never died out.
We love peace,
but we will never tolerate any provocation.
Behind every citizen is a powerful motherland.
And behind our powerful motherland
is an ever-strengthening Chinese military.
We are an invincible force,
always forging ahead
to defend the peace of our motherland and our people.